this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold watcher king of the
pirates monkey luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after reading the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
after being separated from his crew luffy set out to rescue his captured brother ace
to do so he snuck into the government prison impelled down but now he's trying to break back out
ace has been transferred to navy hq for execution and luffy is in desperate pursuit this unprecedented
jailbreak from the bowels of hell itself threatens to boil over into the surrounding sea
but with only four hours until ace's execution will luffy make it in time
new comma kenpo 44 aesthetic technique hair removal
miss the fourth demon god
and that's the warrant
Magellan's Tricky Move, a foiled escape plan.
I've dealt with that fat-headed pervert and his pathetic flunky, too.
Which finally brings me to you.
It's Magellan!
No way!
They can't be dead, can they?
Crap guy!
Eva!
Damn you!
Don't be dumb, Strawboy!
Running is the only option we've got with Magellan!
Let go of me now!
I'm not gonna run, I'm gonna kick his ass!
Yes, sir, but are you sure?
I understand, but that's really what you want?
Yes.
Set up everything just as I've explained, and do it as quickly as possible.
Yes, sir!
All right, we've got our orders from Warden Magellan.
Get backup security.
We're gonna need the help.
Sir!
Damn it.
So that's what he's got on his sleeve.
Damn it!
Just forget it!
You barely laid a finger on him last time, and you're lucky he didn't kill you!
Yeah, but I'm still alive, aren't I?
Miracles don't happen again and again!
That's why they're miracles in the first place!
Quit horse-playing you two, then get to the upper level!
Now, Luffy, we have to get to the main entrance, post-haste!
Things aren't looking good for us.
We were paying too much attention to Magellan.
Don't worry, I got it.
We'll put the plan into motion right now.
Calic!
All right, men!
On the ready!
Get to your position!
Yes, sir!
If you've got a gun, quit running and put some bullets in Magellan!
Shoot him!
Strawboy, stop staring and stop running!
It's pointless!
Those guns aren't even gonna slow him down!
Uh-oh, here it comes!
Time to move, Luffy!
Come on!
Hydra!
Cut off, you guys!
Huh?
Candle wall!
Nice!
Yeah!
He stopped Magellan's hydro right in its tracks!
Your naivety still sickens me, so don't get the wrong idea, all right?
I may have saved your life, but that doesn't mean I want to be friends or any of that mess.
Honestly.
I'm just sick of owing you a damn favor, that's all!
I like you even more now, Brother Three!
Devil fruit powers, huh?
Is that wax?
Yep, precisely!
I ate the wax wax fruit and gained these handy powers.
This wall might as well be made of iron!
I can promise you this!
Your venom is not getting through it!
Hmph.
Glad that pile of garbage was good for something after all.
Just goes to show that every power has a use somewhere or another.
Go!
Get out of here, dammit!
I don't plan on keeping this up forever!
Thanks, man!
Meddlesome twit!
What are you standing around for?
This won't hold much longer!
All right, I'll lead the charge out of here.
You heard him, let's go!
Yeah!
That is super handy!
Outside the burning hill, at least.
Now go and I will be right behind you!
Get a head start and clear the path for us!
Now, Luffy, I'm getting tired of saying it.
Wait, didn't you tell me this would only work if we stole a navy ship?
That's right.
Then why don't you go with everyone else?
I want to stay behind and try to stop this guy.
We're not going to have much chance of stealing it with him chasing us.
That may be the case, but...
Don't you worry, I got a plan.
And you're confident in this?
Yeah, leave it to me.
All right, but don't go and push yourself too hard.
Okay, three, let's get this fight going!
No, hell no!
I don't want to fight that monster!
I was just trying to buy us some time so we can run away!
Run the three!
We aren't that strong, but we're here to help you!
You guys got the wrong idea!
That's not what I want!
Hey, I need you to do me a favor.
I said I'm done with favors!
Get ready, here comes Hydra!
Can you do it?
Well, yes, I suppose it's possible.
It's possible.
Okay, then.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, no pressure or anything!
What works?
Candle!
Over!
Oh, no!
All right, with these on, I'm...
Oh, cool!
Face forward, dammit!
This is not the time to lose your focus!
I'm sorry, but my eyes keep filling up with tears.
Thanks, man.
You made me into an ass-kicking machine.
Just shut up and start fighting!
I almost hate to admit it, but I can't help but admire your tenacity, Straw Hat.
What the hell did you do to Eva?
Ah, I take it you mean Ivankov.
I executed him, of course.
Oh, don't let it worry you.
You can join him soon enough in the afterlife.
Here it comes!
Hydra!
Three!
Right!
I'm on it!
Candle!
Whoa!
Keep trying, but you're not getting through!
Go, go!
Champion!
Rifle!
Awesome!
I can touch him!
These cannons are loaded and good to go!
And we've got candle shields!
Take that! We got the bastard! We can do this!
Listen up! We gotta hold these guys back and buy some time!
Here they come! Open fire!
Who cares if they've got guns? Keep running and break on through!
We're getting close, everyone! Don't slow down on me now!
One final push! Freedom, here I come!
What? None of it worked?
Magellan won't go down easy! Give it everything we got!
Ah!
A-ah!
We beat all the tough guys! That means we can finally relax a bit!
You're letting your guard down.
Don't act like such an amateur.
What?
Going by my last count,
there are at least ten Navy ships waiting out there.
And each one has 800 Marines on board.
I don't know their configuration,
but stealing one Navy ship
means that we're still gonna have to contend
with the rest of the fleet.
Does that sound relaxing to you?
Uh, yeah. You've got a point there.
And that's not the only problem we've got.
There are no more guards to get in our way.
All that's left now is the front door.
We finally made it.
Didn't think I'd see it again,
but there's the entrance to impel down.
I'm sure every last one of us here
remembers the day we passed through the gates of hell.
How many years has it been?
Are we here? Is this really happening?
I'm having trouble believing this is real.
And to think I almost passed on breaking out of this joint.
All right.
Ready your weapons, everyone.
It's time to open this door!
Get ready!
And push!
I finally gotta get to go home!
Shut up!
We're not done yet, so don't jinx it.
There's one last giant hurdle waiting for us out there.
A whole Navy fleet.
So we got a ways to go.
I suppose I see your point.
The list is going to be more challenging than I thought.
Yeah.
But it's not like we should just give up after coming this far.
We might as well push as hard as we can.
Yeah!
It's sunlight!
I can chase this!
I can chase this.
You're a scary monster!
Just don't know why it's a light.
Just don't know why we should have to go.
I'm gonna go!
I suppose I see your point.
The list is going to be more challenging than I thought.
Yeah.
But it's not like we should just give up after coming this far.
We might as well push as hard as we can.
It's sunlight.
I can chase the freedom!
Get ready for the fight of your lives!
I don't care how many thousands of marines are waiting for us,
we're gonna push right through and out to the sea!
It's now or never!
Let's go, boys!
We'll be to freedom!
What the hell?
Is this some kind of sick joke?
Who's got a single lady ship in sight?
What the hell?
Is this some kind of sick joke?
Who's got a single lady ship in sight?
What the hell?
Is this some kind of sick joke?
Not even one Marine!
But this means we're just as trapped as we always were!
It's not fair! What do we do?
The only option left is to just wait here
and hope that Magellan kills us mercifully and quickly.
Dammit! This can't be happening!
They got us.
Gotta give them credit for not being as stupid as I thought they were.
The water around here is filled with giant sea kings.
As the saying goes, the Calm Belt is the greatest barrier protecting Impel Down.
We clawed our way out of the depths of hell with our very fingernails just for this!
Dammit! Now we're gonna get dragged right back into the flames and be tortured!
We don't have time to sit here moping!
Yes, the Navy's gone, but they only cleared out because Magellan told them to.
And they're not far!
Look, and you can see the shadows of their sails on the fog!
He's right!
But they're still too far off!
There's no way we've got a chance of catching them!
But Dad, just accept it's too late!
It's never too late!
You've got me here, right?
So stand back and let me handle this!
Holy crap!
How freakin' strong is he?
He's carrying that door like it was a bag of feathers!
I can't carry many, but this should do!
We can use it to sail out to one of those ships!
If you want to keep moving, hop on!
You really think we can sail out there on a door?
Huh?
Crocodile?
What? Just the two of you? Fine!
Hang on!
Hm?
Don't pretend like you've forgotten about the hero here, you big blue turd!
I know you guys need me, so I'm coming too!
You've got some guts, huh?
That's our Captain Buggy for ya!
Take this baby transponder snail I found!
You know, just in case you need it!
Right!
Come on!
Can't we leave him?
No!
Let's do this!
You ready?
Then here we go!
Yeah!
He's swimming like a shark with that pig on his back!
Now that's the true Captain of the Fishman Pirates!
Oh man!
This is gonna be crazy!
I can't wait to see how the Warlord's gonna fight!
Not to mention our savior Captain Buggy right beside him!
I can't help but feel a little hopeful here!
How stupid are they?
It's a hell of a lot safer to stick with a Warlord than stay behind and try to face Magellan on your own!
Idiots!
Stop!
They're shooting!
Seems like they smarted us!
He dodged it!
He's too fast!
That's not just the Fishman!
That's the first son of the sea, Jinbei!
All forces!
Open fire!
As long as we can sink Jinbei, the rest of them are finished!
Here they are!
An entire fleet of ships!
I'm gonna launch you guys on the deck!
So hold on tight now!
Huh?
Wait, your what?
You maybe wanna run that plan past us one more time, Fish Face?
Huh?
What the...
That bastard's gone!
What the hell's going on?!
I see!
He left us here as bait and scram off on his own!
Traitor!
Traitor Traitor!
Jee Anne!
How can you leave us like this...?
We're sending ducks out here!
They're gonna blast us!
It might help when you stop screaming!
Fishman Jiu-Jitsu!
Waterheart!
It's coming straight forward us!
Fishman!
Ocean current!
Show the throne!
We're flying!
What's with that water column?
It's moving like it's alive!
Do you have any idea what's causing it?
Not the foggiest.
But I can see people on the tip.
One of them's Crocodile!
Up for it!
They're going to try to hijack the ship!
Stop them!
Attack them with everything you've got!
They've got devil fruit powers!
Just throw them in the water!
Oh!
Didn't you learn the first time?
It's a lesson you only get once!
I've got nothing to learn from you!
Come back!
Champion!
Bon Zooka!
So be it.
If you're so insistent on defying me,
then suffer in ignorance
and find your lesson and die!
As Jinbei launches a plan to steal a navy ship,
Luffy battles Magellan with all of his strength.
Determined to win at any cost,
the Warden unleashes his ultimate technique,
which threatens to destroy Impel Down and everyone in it.
On the next, One Piece!
The escapee team in trouble!
The forbidden move!
Venom demon!
I'm going to be king of the pirates!